module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the official Hawaiian state flower?', 
    a: 'Camellia',
    b: 'Yellow hibiscus',
    c: 'Pasque flower',
    d: 'Pink lady\'s slipper',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the tallest mountain in Hawaii?', 
    a: 'Diamond Head',
    b: 'Mauna Loa',
    c: 'Ko\'olau Range',
    d: 'Mauna Kea',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Wreath of flowers presented when arriving or leaving Hawaii?', 
    a: 'Haku',
    b: 'Hilo',
    c: 'Kui',
    d: 'Lei',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hawaii\'s capital city is located on which island?', 
    a: 'Maui',
    b: 'Moloka\'i',
    c: 'Oahu',
    d: 'Island of Hawaii (The Big Island)',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In agriculture, Hawaii is the only state that grows _____', 
    a: 'Sugar Cane',
    b: 'Pineapple',
    c: 'Kiwi Fruit',
    d: 'Coffee',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hawaii\'s official nickname is _____', 
    a: 'Pacific Paradise',
    b: 'The Lei State',
    c: 'The Aloha State',
    d: 'White Sands Beach',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The official Hawaiian fish is called _____', 
    a: 'rectangular triggerfish',
    b: 'Humuhumunukunukuapua\'a',
    c: 'Hawaiian Reef Triggerfish',
    d: 'All of the above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which food is NOT a traditional luau dish?', 
    a: 'Kalua Pork',
    b: 'Lomilomi Salmon',
    c: 'Ajiaco',
    d: 'Poi',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Hawaii\'s all-time record low temperature?', 
    a: '50 F',
    b: '42 F',
    c: '12 F',
    d: '7 F',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Hawaii Volcanoes National Park includes with active volcano?', 
    a: 'Kaho\'olawe',
    b: 'Kilauea',
    c: 'Hale\'akala',
    d: 'Hualalai',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];